{
    "subject": "resource/Operation_Gladio",
    "predicate": "ontology/headquarter",
    "object": "resource/Italy",
    "human_readable": "The headquarters of Operation Gladio are located in Italy.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9655500650405884,
            "question": "Where were the headquarters of Operation Gladio located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9460954070091248,
            "question": "In which country was Operation Gladio headquartered?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5713415741920471,
            "question": "What type of operation was Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5269273519515991,
            "question": "What was the impact of Operation Gladio on Italian society?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41743341088294983,
            "question": "What organization was responsible for Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4157979190349579,
            "question": "When did Operation Gladio take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4100281000137329,
            "question": "What was the purpose of Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2778826653957367,
            "question": "Who were the key players involved in Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27509552240371704,
            "question": "What were the main goals of Operation Gladio?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26790639758110046,
            "question": "Are there any controversies surrounding Operation Gladio?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The headquarters of Operation Gladio are located in Italy.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4529_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were the main goals of Operation Gladio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4529_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were the key players involved in Operation Gladio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4529_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the purpose of Operation Gladio?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4529_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4529_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Gladio\" was a NATO stay-behind organization, and specifically refer to its Italian branch. They also describe the construction of the Gladio headquarters on the Italian island of Sardinia, which further supports the claim that the headquarters are located in Italy."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents do provide information about the existence and operations of Operation Gladio in Italy, including details about its headquarters on the island of Sardinia. Therefore, the statement that the headquarters of Operation Gladio are located in Italy is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Operation Gladio is a NATO operation, and as such, its headquarters are not exclusively or specifically located in Italy. It refers to the clandestine \"stay-behind\" operations in various NATO countries during the Cold War, not just Italy.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}